Guide to the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 61 Records, 1943-1990 AIS.1989.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 61 Records
1943-1990
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America. Local 61 (Neville Island, Pa.)
AIS.1989.05
102.5 Linear Feet (80 boxes and 17 oversize items)
Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 61 was charted in 1943 and represented shipbuilders of the Dravo Corporation in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. During the 1980s, Local 61 found itself in opposition to the activities of the national union's leadership, leading the national union to attempt to revoke the local's charter and its president, Darrell Becker's, membership. This collection includes the records of IUMSWA Local 61, particularly those of president Becker, as well as research files for the Allegheny Conference on Human Development.
Access Restrictions
The membership cards in Boxes 22-24 are closed for 75 years from date of creation. Until this restriction is lifted, access to the cards can be gained by signing a confidentiality agreement. Please contact the Archives Service Center for more information.
Separated Material
Several posters and other oversize items are located in cabinet 3-12.
Related Material
Denominational Ministry Strategy Collection, 1973-1995, AIS.1989.07, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh
D.A. Booth Collection On Dravo Corporation, AIS.1972.09, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
This collection includes correspondence, subject files, agreements, grievances, meeting minutes, and flyers concerning IUMSWA Local 61. Also present are the papers of local president Darrell Becker, which include newspaper clippings, flyers, and legal papers documenting Becker's role in the Denominational Ministry Strategy and Network to Save the Mon/Ohio Valley, as well as his campaign for the presidency of the national union in 1985 and conflicts between the local and the IUMSWA from approximately 1983 to 1988. Research of the Allegheny Conference on Human Development is also present.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Darrell Becker, president of Local 61, in 1989 and 1990.
Arrangement
Series I. Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 61
Series II. Allegheny Conference on Human Development
History
The Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA) was founded in 1934 under the idea of unionizing workers by their industry rather than by their individual trades. In 1935, the IUMSWA affiliated with the Congress of Industrial Organizations. Membership grew during the mobilization of the armed forces during World War II, but the end of the war brought a decline in union membership. Local 61 was charted in 1943 and represented shipbuilders of the Dravo Corporation in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
During the deindustrialization of the 1980s, Darrell Becker, president of Local 61 and member of the Network to Save the Mon/Ohio Valley, claimed that the IUMSWA leadership was cooperating with companies during plant shutdowns. In response, the international union tried to remove Becker from office. When they were unsuccessful, they attempted to revoke the local's charter. In response, Becker ran for president of the national union in 1986. Later, Local 61 and three other locals opposed the national union's plan to merge with the International Association of Machinists (IAM) and encouraged other locals to distance themselves from the national union's leadership in order to make their own independent decision regarding the fate of their locals' affiliation. In 1988, Local 61 left the IUMSWA to become Independent Shipbuilders Union of America Local 61. The IUMSWA merged with the IAM in 1988, but its battle with Becker and Local 61 extended into 1990.
In 1986, Darrell Becker and local activist David Rosenberg of the Neville's Ark food bank created the Allegheny Conference on Human Development (ACHD). This organization was created in response to the Allegheny Conference on Community Development and provided working class people and communities with information on how to defend their jobs and living standards through research and educational programs.
Previous Citation
Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 61 Records, 1943-1990, AIS.1989.05, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Labor disputes -- Pennsylvania -- Neville Island; Labor unions -- Jurisdictional disputes -- United States; Advertising; Neville Island (Pa.); Photographs; Correspondence; Minutes (Administrative records); Clippings (Information artifacts); Legal documents; Shipbuilding industry -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Neville Island; Shipbuilding industry -- Pennsylvania -- Neville Island; Labor; Network to Save the Mon/Ohio Valley; Independent Shipbuilders Union of America. Local 61 (Neville Island, Pa.); Becker, Darrell; Allegheny Conference on Human Development (Pa.); Denominational Ministry Strategy (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America. Local 61 (Neville Island, Pa.)
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 61, I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains the records of IUMSWA Local 61. Included are financial records, membership cards, meeting minutes and correspondence. Also present is information regarding contract negotiations and grievances. Court documents from the case between Local 61 president Darrell Becker and IUMSWA president Arthur Batson, as well as correspondence and fliers from the Denominational Ministry Strategy, are also included.
  - Art Rossi, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Authorization for Examination of Hospital and Medical Records, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Apprentices, Accumulated Time As Of November 1977, December 2, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Buy Back Forms (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Eddie Slocum, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Employees Claim Petition for Compensation, Form LIBC-362 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Forms for Retroactive Contribution Data Retirement Plan (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Frank Ferderbar, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gino's Catering (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Insurance Case, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Joe Kress, Unemployment, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Harry Marchesini, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - John W. Hrapczak, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - John F. Tkach, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kevin Patterson, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agreement between Dravo and Local 61, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Patrick Takash, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Peter Urczyk, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - List of Retirees, December 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Minutes of Marine Ways, August 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Minutes, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Safety Walkaround, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - OSHA Citations and Notification of Penalty, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - OSHA Citation, May 28, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Relocation Letter (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Robert Smallwood, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Shasta Request for Transfer Forms (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - State Workmen's Compensation, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - United Way Information, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ted Pallas, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Ted J. Skepanski, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Unemployment Compensation Review Case, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Basic Steel Agreement, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - W-4 Forms (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Heavy Metals Contract, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - James Edwards, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - John Kovas, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - John Kovac, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - John Simko, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Longshoremen's Act, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Meeting on Marine Ways Minutes, February 14, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bennie Della, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Insurance Claims, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - OSHA Complaint Forms (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Pittsburgh Testing Lab, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Reports to All Locals, Representatives and General Executive Board Members, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Transcript of Arbitration Proceedings, Metallurgical Exoproducts Corporation v. IUMSWA Local 61, April 10, 1970 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - Retirement Proposals Negotiations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Safety, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - S. Muha (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Holiday Inn Meeting Packet, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statement, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Negotiating Committee, 1944-1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Communications, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Strike Negotiation Communications, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Palmerine to Greer, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence, W.E. Clark and Jansen, Dravo Corp., 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania CIO Council Report, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ross D. Blood Correspondence to Local 61, 1953-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Charles Leone, Regional Director, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Grogan - Blood Correspondence, Schulman Attorney, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania AFL-CIO Harrisburg, Labor Reports, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Palmerine Case, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Communications, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Unemployment Compensation Law, Report of Pennsylvania CIO Council, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Strike Communications: Negotiations, 1944-1947 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Minutes of Negotiations between Local 61 and Dravo, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Local 61 Unemployment Compensation Case, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Allegheny County Labor Council, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Palmerine to Greer and Mervin, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Communications, 1955, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
  - Report on Pennsylvania CIO Council, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania CIO Council, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Armand Palmerine Negotiation File, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
  - Minutes, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Trustee Reports, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Berth Descriptions, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Local 61 Arbitrations with Dravo Corp., 1944-1946 (Box 4, Item 1-5)
  - Negotiations, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Changes in By-Laws, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Negotiations with Dravo, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Eugene Victor Molte NLRB Case, IUMSWA v. Dravo (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Easter Hams, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Local 61 By-Laws and Correspondence with the National Office, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1952-1957 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NLRB Inspectors, Febraury 3, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Joseph Dunlevy Trial Board, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bonus, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - By-Laws, 1953, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Pittsburgh Coke and Chemical Picnic Personnel Manager, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania Industrial Safety Conference, 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Employees Claim Petition for Compensation for Disability (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Keystone and Union Barge Supplemental Agreement, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Boxing Committee, "750" LST, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - War Price Board and Office of Price Administration Priorities, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Affidavit of Non-Communist Organization, 1952-1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Waivers, Lift Waivers, Terminations, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Negotiation Minutes, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Labor Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Blood - Williams Communications, General Executive Board, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Thornburg's File, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Negotiations, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Communications, Greer - Dravo Corp., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Communications, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Waiver Terminations and Retirees, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Blood - Grogan and Leone - Dekleva, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - By-Laws, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Vardzel amd Fekete Court Cases, Attorney Slyvan Libson, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Communications: Leone - Grogan and Blood - Dekelva, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Pension Negotiations, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - General Executive Board Condensed Financial Report, July 31, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Annual Picnic Report, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Communications, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Communications: Thornburg - Greer, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Letters, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Job Communications, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Waivers, Waiver Lifts and Terminations, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Eddie Slocum Case, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Benak Fuchs Trial Board, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sabatino (Sam) Calcaterra, Metallurgical Exoproducts Plant Accident, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Disability, Dravo Group Insurance, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Group Insurance Cancellations, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Greer Communications, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Thornburg Special File, 1959-1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Communications, November 1974-December 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14-23)
  - Grievances, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - List of Classifications, June 8, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - LMP Job Classifications, June 8, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Heavy Metal Job Classification List, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Stewards, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Classification List, July 13, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Employee Relocation List, December 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Communications, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 8-10)
  - HMP Communications, October-November 1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Aggregates Communications, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 12-14)
  - LMP Communications, November-December 1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Boatyard Unemployment, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Retirement Letters from National Union, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - US Court of Appeals, Dravo Crop., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Resolution, 30th National Convention and Amendments to the Constitution, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 30th National Convention, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Names and Addresses of Employees, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - OSHA: Your Workplace Rights in Action (Box 7, Item 1-3)
  - Dravo Corp. Retirement Plan, 1965-1979 (Box 7, Item 4-9)
  - Dravo Corp. Dental Insurance Program, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Item 10-22)
  - Dravo Corp. Group Insurance Program, 1968-1982 (Box 7, Item 23-33)
  - How to Run a Union Meeting by AFL-CIO (Box 7, Item 34)
  - Blue Cross Coverage: A Handbook for Active Employees and Eligible Retirees of Dravo Corporation and Subsidiaries, 1981 (Box 7, Item 35)
  - Agreements between Dravo Corp. and IUMSWA Local 61, 1954-1983 (Box 7, Item 36-71)
  - Constitution of the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1958-1970, 1976-1984 (Box 7, Item 72-88)
  - Constitution of the International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1981 (Box 7, Item 89)
  - By-Laws of IUMSWA Local 61, 1953, 1963, 1973 (Box 7, Item 90-94)
  - By-Laws of IUMSWA Local 9, 1976 (Box 7, Item 95)
  - By-Laws of Shopmen's Local Union No. 627, International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1961 (Box 7, Item 96)
  - Agreement between General Dynamics Quincy Shipbuilding Division and IUMSWA Local 5, 1980 (Box 7, Item 97)
  - Agreement between Bath Iron Works Corp. and IUMSWA Local 6, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Item 98)
  - Agreement between Todd Pacific Shipyards Corp. and IUMSWA Local 9, 1983 (Box 7, Item 99)
  - New Pension Reform Highlights, IUMSWA, 1974 (Box 7, Item 100)
  - Safety Practices Cards (Box 7, Item 101)
  - IUMSWA Convention Proceedings, 1968-1984 (Box 7, Item 102-111)
  - Relationships by Objectives, Samples and Guidelines, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Relationships by Objectives, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Officers and Committees, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dues Refund, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
  - Apprenticeship Information, Machine Shop and Mold Loft, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Occupation Lists, December 1982-August 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7-15)
  - Cost of Living Information, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut General Master Insurance Plan, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - Trial Board, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Safety Data, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Shift Change Letter, Original LMP (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Policy Making Seminar, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Mini Relationships by Objectives Meetings, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Request for Pension Buy Back, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - HMP List of Family Composition Cards, April 30, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Job Descriptions, EWD - Heavy Metals, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - LMP Communications, 1967, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 27-38)
  - Labor Management Reports, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Contract Agreement Materials (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Internal Correspondence, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - List of Retirees, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Agreement between Dravo Corp. and IUMSWA Local 61, 1943-1980 (Box 8, Item 1-17)
  - Dravo Corp., Neville Island Grating Plant Agreement, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Agreement between Jeffboat Inc. and General Drivers Warehousemen and Helpers, Local 89 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Agreement between Dravo Corp. and IUMSWA Local 61, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Notebook (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration, Shasta Inc. and IUMSWA Local 61, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6-8)
  - Dravo Corp. and IUMSWA Local 61 Benefits, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - General Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local 89 Information, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Employment Applications (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Pension and Insurance, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Timekeepers, Mr. Lippard, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Social Security Information, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Panels, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Forms for Request for Arbitration Panel (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Longshoremen, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Forms, Longshoremen (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Longshoremen's Revision, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Longshoremen's Cases, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Dick Dwyer, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Picnic, July 11, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Occupational I-11 Data, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Light Metals Plant Grievances, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - National Labor Relations Board Case, March 5, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pay Board, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Pay Board, Cost of Living Adjustment and Forecast, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
  - Light Metals, List of Employees and Wages, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Retirement Letters from National Union, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Retroactive Pay, February 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Safety Data Sheet for Boatyard, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Standard By-Laws from National Union, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - US Department of Labor Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - US Immigration Laws, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Information, Strikes, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - LMP Job Classification, June 10, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Job Description, Albert J. Maccarone, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - HMP Job Classifications, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
  - Light Metals Plant Contract, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Financial Statement, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Job Classifications and Wage Rate (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - By-Laws Committee, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - International General Executive Board Reports, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - IUMSWA Resolutions and Extra Amendments, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Strike Fund Deposit Slips, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Application Cards for Union Membership, 1976 (Box 10, Item 1)
  - Job Descriptions, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Grievances, 1960-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration, 1968-1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Typed Minutes, 1960-1965 (Box 11, Folder 4-9)
  - Handwritten Minute Book, 1961-1971 (Box 11, Item 1)
  - Minutes, 1966-1979 (Box 12)
  - Minutes, 1980, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Item 1-4)
  - Blank Meeting Minute Forms (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Elected Officers and Committees, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - By-Laws (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Communications, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 2-36)
  - Penguins Hockey Night Forms, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Grievance Letters to Arbitrate, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Elections, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Election Results (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Dravo Retirement Plan, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Retirees, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 8-19)
  - List of Retirees, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Retiree Letter Blanks for National Union (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Retirement Letters from National Union to Retirees, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
  - Retirement Information, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Retirement Plans for Employees of Dravo Corp., December 18, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Letters to National Retirees, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Truweld, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 27-28)
  - Truweld Strike Vote, October 1, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Light Metals Pension Plan and Information, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Employee Welfare or Pension Benefit Plan Annual Report Form, 1968-1974 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Case Against Maggio, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Shasta Contracts, 1981, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 33-34)
  - Pension Agreement, Metscrap, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Dravo-Mechling Negotiations, May 1983 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Metscrap Division I and II Agreement, 1977-1983 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Metscrap Negotiations, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Dravo-Mechling Agreement, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Metscrap Contract Negotiations and Vote, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Truweld Contract, 1959-1983 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Agreements between Dravo Corp. and IUMSWA Local 61, 1959-1986 (Box 15, Item 1)
  - Agreements between McKees Rocks Packaging Co. and IUMSWA, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Item 2)
  - Agreements with Metallurgical Exoproduct, 1981 (Box 15, Item 3)
  - Dravo Group Insurance Plan, 1977 (Box 15, Item 4)
  - Dravo Retirement Plans, 1971, 1978 (Box 15, Item 5)
  - Dravo Correspondence to Employees, 1983 (Box 15, Item 6)
  - Harpoon by IUMSWA, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Item 1)
  - IUMSWA LM Reports, 1982-1985 (Box 16, Item 2)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1985 (Box 16, Item 3)
  - United Labor Action, 1987 (Box 16, Item 4)
  - Multinational Monitor, 1986 (Box 16, Item 5)
  - Magazines and Pamphlets, 1985-1987 (Box 16, Item 6)
  - Media, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Information, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - T.S., Correspondence, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Labor Report Hourly Payroll, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Administration of the Labor Contract (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Internal Correspondence, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dravo Fact Sheet (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Save Our Shipbuilders, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - IUMSWA, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Save Our Shipbuilders Correspondence, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - National Labor Relations Board v. Batson, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - US Steel, 1984, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Union Book, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Truweld, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Truweld Recertification, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Truweld Trusteeship, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Labor Board, Shasta, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Actuarial Reports, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Local 61 v. IUMSWA, 1985-1987 (Box 19)
  - Strike Benefits, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Truweld Communications, May 1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)